Guide to the Robert J. Levine Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Office Files, 1962-1997; Series II
  - Cannon, Cynthia, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Carlson, John, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Carney, Frederick S., 1975-1985 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Carney, Mary, Undated (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Carr, Edward, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Carrier Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Carter, Levi, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Casey, J. Gregory, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Casimir, Bartholomew, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Cato, Allen, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Cayer, Arlene, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - CBS Morning News, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - Cedarbaum, Jesse, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Cerrico, Janice, Undated (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Chalk, Rosemary, 1981-1992 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Chalmers, Andy, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Chan, Carlysle, Undated (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Chapman, Carleton, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Chaudry, Irshad, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Chayet, Neil, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 127-128)
  - Cheetham, Donald, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Chervenak, Frank, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Chiacchierini, Richard, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - Chodos, Robert B., 1982 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Christiansen, Ed, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - CIBA-GEIGY Corporation, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Clarfield, A. Mark, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Clarke, Peter, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Clements, Colleen, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Clinical Research Practices and Drug Regulatory Affairs, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Clinical Resources Inc., Undated (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Cobb, Sanford, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Cockburn, W. Charles, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Code, Charles F., 1966-1978 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Codish, Kay, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Cohen, Kenneth, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Cohen, Peter, Undated (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Cohen, Sanford, 1975-1984 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Cole, Thomas, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Coleman, Michael J., 1973-1978 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Conn, Harold O., 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Connecticut Nurses Association, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Connelly, Julia, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Connelly, William, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Conrad, Constance C., 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Contant, Tracy, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Continuing Education, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Cooke, Robert E., 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Cooney, Gene, Circa 1992 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Cooney, Leo M., 1984 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Cornelius, Eugene, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Crane, Lansing, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Cranford, Ronald, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Crede, William, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Crispin, Joanne, Undated (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Crout, J. Richard, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Cuca, Janet, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Culver, Charles, 1981-1989 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Cummings, Steven R., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Cunningham, Nance, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - Curran, William, 1973-1991 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Curti, Joseph T., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Cypess, Ray, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - Daniel, Rodny, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Daniels, Marcia, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Danisa, Kola, 1970-1983 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Davis-Aimesbury, Marion, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Deardon, John, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - DeBakey, Lois, 1975-1988 (Box 11, Folder 177-179)
  - DeBakey, Lois, 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 180)
  - De Deyn, P. P., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 181)
  - DeFelice, Stephen, 1973-1989 (Box 12, Folder 182)
  - De Figueiredo, John, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 183)
  - Delano, Susan, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - Dellinger, R. Phillip, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 185)
  - Del Tacca, Mario, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 186)
  - de Maagd, Emogene, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 187)
  - Dempsey, Luke, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 188)
  - Desan, Paul, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 189)
  - Detre, Thomas, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 190)
  - Devous, Michael, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 191)
  - Diamond, Jack, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 192)
  - Dillon, Wilton, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 193)
  - Dirks, John, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 194)
  - DiSabatino, Charles, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 195)
  - Djahanguiri, Bijon, 1972-1984 (Box 12, Folder 196)
  - Doherty, James, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 197)
  - Dolan, Susan, Undated (Box 12, Folder 198)
  - Dolnansky, Ellen, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 199)
  - Donovan, Constance, 1978-1993 (Box 12, Folder 200)
  - Donovan, Raymond, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 201)
  - Dossetor, John, 1985-1989 (Box 12, Folder 202)
  - Downey, Linda, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 203)
  - Drysdale, Philip, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 204)
  - Duff, Ray, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 205)
  - Dukes, M. N. Graham, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 206)
  - Dull, Bruce, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 207)
  - Duncombe, David, 1973-1988 (Box 12, Folder 208)
  - Dunham, Nancy, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 209)
  - Dustan, Harriet, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Dyess, Cynthia, 1982-1986 (Box 12, Folder 211)
  - Easterbrook, Philippa, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 212)
  - Ebbert, Arthur, 1969-1983 (Box 12, Folder 213)
  - Eddy, David, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 214)
  - Edge, Dana, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 215)
  - Edwards, Rem B., 1986 (Box 12, Folder 216)
  - Effa, Pierre, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 217)
  - Eisenberg, Leon, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 218)
  - Eisenberg, Lester, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 219)
  - Eisenfeld, Arnold, 1971-1987 (Box 12, Folder 220)
  - Eisenfeld, Leonard, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 221)
  - Ellis, Judith, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 222)
  - Engelman, Karl, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 223)
  - Enlow, Roger W., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 224)
  - Epstein, Frank, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 225)
  - Ernstoff, Marc, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 226)
  - Eser, Albin, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 227)
  - Estep, Trish, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 228)
  - Everist, Hilleary, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 229)
  - Fasano, Anthony, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 230)
  - Fasting, Ulla, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 231)
  - Fay, Kathleen, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 232)
  - Fearon, Richard, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 233)
  - Felch, William C., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 234)
  - Felder, Michael, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 235)
  - Felig, Philip, 1971-1988 (Box 12, Folder 236)
  - Fenn, John, 1983-1990 (Box 12, Folder 237)
  - Fenney, Nicholas, 1976-1987 (Box 12, Folder 238)
  - Ferris, Thomas, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 239)
  - Fetter, Robert, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 240)
  - Few, Barbara, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 241)
  - Field, William, 1985, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 243)
  - Fielden-Smith, Lynn, 1979-1982 (Box 12, Folder 244)
  - Fields, William, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 245)
  - Fitzgerald, Faith, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - Fitzpatrick, James, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 247)
  - Fleming, Douglas, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 242)
  - Fletcher, Joseph, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 248)
  - Food and Drug Administration, Nancy Cherry, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 249)
  - Fordis, Michael, 1982-1992 (Box 12, Folder 250)
  - Fordyce, Alice, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 251)
  - Forget, Bernadette, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 252)
  - Forget, Bernard, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 253)
  - Forret, Patricia, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 254)
  - Fox, Richard, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 255)
  - Fracchia, Giovanni, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 256)
  - Fracture Intervention Trial, 1992-1996 (Box 13, Folder 257)
  - Francke, Uta, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 258)
  - Freishtat, Harvey, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 259)
  - Fried, Charles, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 260)
  - Friendly, Fred, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 261)
  - Frohlich, Edward, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 262)
  - Fudenberg, Hugh H., 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 263)
  - Furrow, Barry, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 264)
  - Gable, Robert, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 265)
  - Gaffney, Thomas E., 1962-1984 (Box 13, Folder 266)
  - Gagnon, James, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 267)
  - Gallant, Dean, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 268)
  - Galvin, Charles O., 1977-1987 (Box 13, Folder 269)
  - Gangi, D. P., 1984 (Box 13, Folder 270)
  - Garcia Alonso, Diego M., 1990 (Box 13, Folder 271)
  - Garrell, Marvin, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 272)
  - Gaylin, Willard, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 273)
  - Gee, Bernard, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 274)
  - Geertsma, Mary Anne, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 275)
  - Geyman, John, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 276)
  - Giamatti, A. Bartlett, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 277)
  - Giarman, Nicholas J., 1965-1986 (Box 13, Folder 278)
  - Glaser, Gilbert, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 279)
  - Glazer, John, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 280)
  - Glendon Association, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 281)
  - Glenn, William, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 282)
  - Goldberg, Leon, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 283)
  - Goldenberg, Ira, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 284)
  - Goldfinger, Stephen, 1974-1979 (Box 13, Folder 285)
  - Golding, Martin, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 286)
  - Goldstein, Irwin, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 287)
  - Goldstein, Joseph, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 288)
  - Goodyear, Allan V. N., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 289)
  - Gorman, Warren, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 290)
  - Gotto, Antonio, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 291)
  - Goyer, Robert, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 292)
  - Gradman, Alan, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 293)
  - Graffeo, Genevieve, 1981-1986 (Box 13, Folder 294)
  - Grafflin, Marjorie, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 295)
  - Graham, Cheryl, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 296)
  - Gramelspacher, Gregory, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 297)
  - Grant, Elaine, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 298)
  - Grant, Michael, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 299)
  - Grasso, Ella, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 300)
  - Graubard, Stephen, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 301)
  - Gravelle, Karen, Undated (Box 13, Folder 302)
  - Gray, Frieda, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 303)
  - Gray, Hanna, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 304)
  - Grazier, Kyle, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 305)
  - Greeley, Henry T., 1993 (Box 13, Folder 306)
  - Greene, Nicholas, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 307)
  - Greenspan, Richard, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 308)
  - Gremvik, Ake, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 309)
  - Griffith, Robert W., 1983-1992 (Box 13, Folder 310)
  - Grim, Pamela, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 311)
  - Grossman, Hillel, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 312)
  - Grudner, T. M., 1980-1982 (Box 13, Folder 313)
  - Grundstein, Rivka, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 314)
  - Gryboski, Joyce, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 315)
  - Gupta, Sudhir, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 316)
  - Guth, William, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 317)
  - Gwatkin, Phyllis, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 318)
  - Hadjimichael, Jane, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 319)
  - Haggerty, Robert, International Pediatric Association, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 320)
  - Hall, Diana, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 321)
  - Hamburg, David, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 322)
  - Hammershaimb, Luz, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 323)
  - Hammond, Janet, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 324)
  - Hardy, Ellen, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 325)
  - Hardy, Leslie, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 326)
  - Harrington, Mark, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 328)
  - Harris, Ted, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 327)
  - Harrison, Donald, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 329)
  - Harrison, Suzanne D., 1982 (Box 13, Folder 330)
  - Hart, Diana, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 331)
  - Harvey, Mary, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 332)
  - Hassner, Vera, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 333)
  - Hastings Workshops, 1976-1986 (Box 13, Folder 334-336)
  - Hausen, Arthur, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 337)
  - Haynes, R. Brian, 1979-1986 (Box 14, Folder 338)
  - Hayslett, John P., 1977 (Box 14, Folder 339)
  - Health Professionals for the Prevention of Nuclear War, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 340)
  - Healy, Jay, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 341)
  - Heavner, James, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 342)
  - Heifitz, Milton, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 343)
  - Henderson, Gail, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 344)
  - Hendrix, Thomas R., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 345)
  - Henningfield, Jack, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 346)
  - Herbert, Victor, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 347)
  - Hersen, Michael, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 348)
  - Hersh, Donna, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 349)
    - Additional material, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 353)
  - Herting, Robert, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 350)
  - Hewitt, Jan L., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 351)
  - Hines, Chesley, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 352)
  - Hirschhorn, Kurt, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 354)
  - Hobbins, John, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 355)
  - Hoffer, Paul B., 1977 (Box 14, Folder 356)
  - Hoffman, Joe, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 357)
  - Holbrook, Karen, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 358)
  - Hood, William, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 359)
  - Horsburgh, C. Robert, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 360)
  - Horsfall, Amanda, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 361)
  - Horwitz, Melvin, Circa 1985 (Box 14, Folder 362)
  - Houghland, James, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 363)
  - Howard, Beth, Undated (Box 14, Folder 364)
  - Howard, Debra, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 365)
  - Hudson, Robert P., 1978 (Box 14, Folder 366)
  - Huff, Thomas, 1978-1982 (Box 14, Folder 367)
  - Hughes, Jack, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 368)
  - Hughes, Virginia, 1987-circa 1990 (Box 14, Folder 369)
  - Hull, Richard T., 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 370)
  - Hunt, Cuy and Marion Hunt, Undated (Box 14, Folder 371)
  - Hunt, Morton, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 372)
  - Hurd, Suzanne, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 373)
  - Hurst, Marilyn, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 374)
  - Huszar, Gabor, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 375)
  - Huth, Edward, 1973-1990 (Box 14, Folder 376)
  - Hyde, Fred, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 377)
  - Hypertension, prescription guides, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 378)
  - Iannone, Gale, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 379)
  - Iber, Frank, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 380)
  - Illhardt, F. J., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 381)
  - Industrial Biotechnology Association, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 382)
  - Ingelfinger, Franz, 1970-1980 (Box 14, Folder 383)
  - Ingram, Roland, 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 384)
  - Institute of Medicine
    - Drafts, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 385)
    - Manning, Frederick (FAIU), 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 386)
    - Women in clinical studies, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 387)
  - International Clinical Epidemiology Network (INCLEN), 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 388-389)
  - Jacobs, Leonard S., 1986 (Box 14, Folder 390)
  - Jacobson, James, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 391)
  - James, Everette, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 392)
  - Janerich, Dwight, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 393)
  - Jensen, Birthe, 1990-1993 (Box 14, Folder 394)
  - Johnson, Nancy, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 395)
  - Journal of Family Practice, 1975-1989 (Box 14, Folder 396)
  - Kalish, Stephen, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 397)
  - Kanoti, George, 1988-1993 (Box 14, Folder 398)
  - Kaplan, Ed, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 399)
  - Kaplow, Leonard, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 400)
  - Kase, Nathan, 1964-1982 (Box 14, Folder 401)
  - Katz, Maidi, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 402)
  - Katz, Ronald, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 403)
  - Kavirajan, Harish, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 404)
  - Kaye, Michael, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 405)
  - Kelaghan, Joe, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 406)
  - Kellogg, Gus, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 407)
  - Kelman, Herbert, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 408)
  - Kelmowitz, Robert, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 409)
  - Kelsey, Francis, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 410)
  - Kemper, Kathi, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 411)
  - Kernan, Walter, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 412)
  - Kessler, Janice, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 413)
  - Keystone Center for Continuing Education, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 414-415)
  - Kibbe, Arthur, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 416)
  - Kikaku, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 417)
  - King, Andrea, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 418)
  - King, Elihu, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 419)
  - Kinney, Marguerite, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 420)
  - Kirsch, Tom, Undated (Box 15, Folder 421)
  - Kirschstein, Ruth, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 422)
  - Klaus, Sidney, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 423)
  - Kleber, Herb, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 424)
  - Klein, David L., 1989 (Box 15, Folder 425)
  - Klein, Lee, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 426)
  - Kleinig, John, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 427)
  - Klerman, Gerald, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 428)
  - Klocke, Francis, 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 429)
  - Klocke, Robert, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 430)
  - Koering, Marilyn, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 431)
  - Komp, Diane, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 432)
  - Krauss, Alfred, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 433)
  - Krilly, Pamela, Undated (Box 15, Folder 434)
  - Krizek, Claudette, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 435)
  - Kushlan, Samuel, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 436)
  - Kutscher, Austin, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 437)
  - Lachs, John, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 438)
  - Landau, Richard, 1976-1980 (Box 15, Folder 439)
  - Landesman, Sheldon, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 440)
  - Landsberg, Lewis, 1969-1985 (Box 15, Folder 441)
  - Landwirth, Julius, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 442)
  - Lang, Robert, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 443)
  - Laor, Nathaniel, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 444)
  - Lappe, Marc, 1975-1989 (Box 15, Folder 445)
  - LaPuma, John, 1989-1994 (Box 15, Folder 446)
  - Lauler, David, 1978-1983 (Box 15, Folder 447)
  - Lavori, Philip, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 448)
  - Lawrence, Dale, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 449)
  - Lee, Bonnie, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 450)
  - Lee, Richard V., 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 451)
  - Leigh, Hoyle, 1974-1989 (Box 15, Folder 452)
  - Leiter, Elliot, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 453)
  - Lenow, Jeffrey, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 454)
  - Lepp, Bruce, 1982-1985 (Box 15, Folder 455)
  - Levine, Elaine, Undated (Box 15, Folder 456)
  - Levine, Herbert, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 457)
  - Levis, Albert, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 458)
  - Levitin, Howard, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 459)
  - Levy, Daniel, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 460)
  - Levy, Robert I., 1977-1993 (Box 15, Folder 461)
  - Lewis, Melvin, 1979-1996 (Box 15, Folder 462)
  - Ley, Emeen, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 463)
  - Liebenluft, Robert, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 464)
  - Liebman, Theodor, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 465)
  - Lietman, Paul, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 466-467)
  - Lifland, Howard, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 468)
  - Lin, Felix, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 469)
  - Lindblad, Anne, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 470)
  - Linville, Patricia, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 471)
  - Lipsey, Lewis, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 472)
  - Lockhart, Jean, 1975-1978, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 473)
  - Lowe, Beth, Undated (Box 15, Folder 474)
  - Lowendorf, Henry, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 475)
  - Lowy, Frederick, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 476)
  - Ludbrook, Philip, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 477)
  - Lynn, Joanne, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 478)
  - Lyons, Judy, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 479)
  - Lyons, Roger, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 480)
  - MacDonald, Alan S., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 481)
  - MacFarley, David, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 482)
  - Machata, Karl, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 483)
  - Macklin, Ruth, 1981-1985 (Box 16, Folder 484-485)
  - MacLeod, Gordon, 1968-1982 (Box 16, Folder 486)
  - Madden, Josh, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 487)
  - Maiuri, Renard, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 488)
  - Malawista, Stephen, 1971-1983 (Box 16, Folder 489)
  - Manchester, William, 1977-1988 (Box 16, Folder 490)
  - Mann, Michael, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 491)
  - Marks, William, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 492)
  - Marsh, John, 1979-1984 (Box 16, Folder 493)
  - Marshall, Julie, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 494)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital (MSG) Institute, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 495)
  - Massad, Susan, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 496)
  - Matoren, Gary, 1981-1991 (Box 16, Folder 497)
  - Mattison, Nancy, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 498)
  - Mazur, G. O., 1988 (Box 16, Folder 499)
  - McCann, Diana, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 500)
  - McCarthy, James, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 501)
  - McCloy, Stuart, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 502)
  - McCollum, Robert, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 503)
  - McEwan, Peter, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 504)
  - McIntyre, Russell, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 505)
  - McMahon, Laurence, 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 506)
  - McMillan, Claude, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 507)
  - McMullin, Barbara, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 508)
  - Medicine for the 21st Century, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 509)
  - Medicine, Society and Public Health Study Group, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 510)
  - Melmon, Ken, 1969-1984 (Box 16, Folder 511)
  - Melnick, Vijaya, 1981-1985 (Box 16, Folder 512)
  - Melton, Gary, 1986-1989 (Box 16, Folder 513)
  - Mendelsohn, Jack, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 514)
  - Meng Cheong Wong, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 515)
  - Merendino, Jack, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 516)
  - Merikangas, James, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 517)
  - Metz, Stewart, 1971-1991 (Box 16, Folder 518-519)
  - Meyer, Roger, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 520)
  - Miké, Valerie, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 521)
  - Miller, Frank N., Jr., 1975 (Box 16, Folder 522)
  - Miller, Judith, 1984-1992 (Box 16, Folder 523-526)
  - Miller, Robert D., 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 527)
  - Miller, Ron, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 528)
  - Millstein, Lloyd, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 529)
  - Mockovak, Michael, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 530)
  - Moleski, Ron, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 531)
  - Mongillo, Anna, Undated (Box 16, Folder 532)
  - Mooney, Chris, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 533)
  - Mordacci, Roberto, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 534)
  - Mordavsky, Donald, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 535)
  - Morgan, Robert, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 536)
  - Morganthau, Joan, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 537)
  - Morris, Carl, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 538)
  - Morris, John McL., 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 539)
  - Morris, Louis A., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 540)
  - Morris, Thomas Q., 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 541)
  - Moseley, Ray, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 542)
  - Moser, Robert, 1974-1982 (Box 17, Folder 543)
  - Moskowitz, Ellen, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 544)
  - Mullaney, Stephanie, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 545)
  - Munar, Wolfgang, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 546)
  - Mundinger, Mary, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 547)
  - Myers, Martin, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 548)
  - Natanson, Maurice, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 549)
  - National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute (NHLBI) Data and Safety Monitoring Board (DSMB)
    - Cardioverter, 1993-1997 (Box 17, Folder 550)
    - Infant heart surgery, 1989-1995 (Box 17, Folder 551-552)
    - Novacor, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 553)
  - Needell, Mervin, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 554)
  - Nelson, John, Undated (Box 17, Folder 555)
  - Nelson, Larry, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 556)
  - Newton, Lisa, 1980-1992 (Box 17, Folder 557-561)
  - Nicholas, John M., 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 562)
  - Nightingale, Tom, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 563)
  - Nikkei Medical, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 564)
  - Noach, E. L., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 565)
  - Nolan, Richard, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 566)
  - Nordhoff, Henry, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 567)
  - Noyes, Marjorie, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 568)
  - Nursing, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 569)
  - Oates, John A., 1965-1989 (Box 17, Folder 570)
  - Oberkirch, Ann, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 571)
  - O'Brian, Dennis, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 572)
  - O'Connor, Richard, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 573)
  - Office of Protection from Research Risks (OPRR): Bentz, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 574)
  - Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 575-576)
  - Office of Technology Assessment (OTA): Vaccines, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 577)
  - O'Hare, Jean, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 578)
  - O'Keefe, Elaine, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 579)
  - Olsson, Ray A., 1980 (Box 17, Folder 580)
  - Omenn, Gilbert, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 581)
  - Oncology Investigation Committee, 1989-1993 (Box 17, Folder 582-583)
  - O'Neill, John, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 584)
  - Osterweis, Marian, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 585)
  - Owen, Susan, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 586)
  - Paltrow, Lynn, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 587)
  - Papac, Rose J., 1981 (Box 18, Folder 588)
  - Papirno, Elissa, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 589)
  - Parks, Wade, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 590)
  - Patterson, Roy, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 591)
  - Pawelek, John, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 592)
  - Pearl, Robin, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 593)
  - Pearse, Warren, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 594)
  - Pearson, Dave, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 595)
  - Penzer, Jason, Undated (Box 18, Folder 596)
  - Perlman, Max, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 597)
  - Perratt, Mary, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 598)
  - Perry, Seymour, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 599)
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1977-1979 (Box 18, Folder 600)
  - Peskin, Gerald, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 601)
  - Peskin, Steven, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 602)
  - Peterson, Ralph, 1984-1987 (Box 18, Folder 603)
  - Petricciani, John, 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 604)